TOKEN	NE-COARSE-LIT	NE-COARSE-METO	NE-FINE-LIT	NE-FINE-METO	NE-FINE-COMP	NE-NESTED	NEL-LIT	NEL-METO	MISC
# hipe2022:original_source = data/preparation/corpus/en/retokenized/cu31924087948174_0078.xmi
# hipe2022:license = CC-BY
# hipe2022:language = en
# hipe2022:document_type = commentary
# hipe2022:document_id = cu31924087948174_0078
# hipe2022:date = 1881-01-01
# hipe2022:dataset = ajmc
# hipe2022:applicable_columns = TOKEN NE-COARSE-LIT NE-FINE-LIT NE-NESTED NEL-LIT MISC
# ajmc:version = v0.4
# ajmc:title = Sophocles
# ajmc:publication_place = Oxford
# ajmc:publication_date = 1881
# ajmc:page = 78
# ajmc:author = Campbell, Lewis
413	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πόροι	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἁλίρροθοι	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
]	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
‘Paths	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
surging	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
sea	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
”	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
i	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
e	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
either	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
generally	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
or	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
with	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
reference	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
narrow	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
seas	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Aegean	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
called	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πόντιαι	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
adA@ves	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Trach	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q945342	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q945342	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
100	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
which	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
separated	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ajax	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q172725	_	LED0.00
from	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
his	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
home	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
or	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
possibly	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Hellespont	B-loc	_	B-loc	_	_	O	Q6514	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
which	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
had	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
witnessed	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
his	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
exploits	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
called	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Xerxes	B-pers	_	B-pers.other	_	_	O	Q18217408	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Hdt	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q26825	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q26825	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
7	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
35	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἁλμυρὸς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ποταμός	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
infr	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
884	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Aesch	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q40939	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.17
,	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q40939	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.17
Pers	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q788458	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q788458	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
367	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
414	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πάραλά	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
τ᾽	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἄντρα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κιτιλ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
These	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
were	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
especially	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
familiar	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ajax	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q172725	_	LED0.00
from	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
his	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
position	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
at	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
end	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
line	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
towards	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Rhoeteum	B-loc	_	B-loc	_	_	O	Q7321268	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
416	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀμπνοὰς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἔχοντα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
]	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
i	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
e	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
‘If	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
you	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
keep	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
me	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
here	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
will	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
not	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
be	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
life	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
417	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
φρονῶν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
]	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
‘If	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
he	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
have	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
sense	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
perceive	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
”	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
420	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
elippoves	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
᾿Αργείοις	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
]	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
i	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
e	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
«Kind	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
me	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
no	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
longer	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
but	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
my	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
enemies	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
In	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
different	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
mood	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
he	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
afterwards	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
infr	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
863	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
bids	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
farewell	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
rivers	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Troy	B-loc	_	B-loc	_	_	O	Q22647	_	LED0.00
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
his	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
nurses	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
424	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οἷον	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
τ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
λ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
]	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
In	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Homeric	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
fashion	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ajax	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q172725	_	LED0.00
boasts	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
himself	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
be	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
bravest	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Greeks	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Il	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q8275	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q8275	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
18	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
104	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
5	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
τοῖος	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἐὼν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οἷος	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οὔτις	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
᾿Αχαιῶν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
χαλκοχιτώνων	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
|	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἐν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πολέμῳ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
That	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
he	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
bravest	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
next	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Achilles	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q41746	_	LED0.00
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Homeric	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
tradition	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
he	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
acknowledged	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
be	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
so	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
his	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
enemy	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Odysseus	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q47231	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
infr	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
1341	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
arrangement	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
this	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
part	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
antistrophe	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
must	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
be	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
adapted	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
change	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
made	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
strophe	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
See	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
note	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
on	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
405	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
foll	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence|InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
For	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
μέγα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Pind	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q134929	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q134929	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Nem	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q27214182	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q27214182	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
6	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
45	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
6	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἔλπομαι	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
μέγα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
εἰπὼν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
σκοποῦ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἄντα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
τυχεῖν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
425	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
hiatus	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
after	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀπό	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
at	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
end	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
lyric	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
iambic	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
line	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
doubtful	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
427	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
reading	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πρόκειται	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
not	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
wholly	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
impossible	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
428	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οὔθ᾽	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ὅπως	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
]	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Elmsley	B-pers	_	B-pers.editor	_	_	O	Q7173848	_	LED0.00
would	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
read	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οὐδ᾽	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
because	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
there	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
no	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
τε	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
preceding	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
But	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
this	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
too	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
strict	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
430	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
011	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
For	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
pijois	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
similarly	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
following	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
μέλη	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀπὸ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
σκηνῆς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
EL	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q733444	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.67
254	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence|InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
