TOKEN	NE-COARSE-LIT	NE-COARSE-METO	NE-FINE-LIT	NE-FINE-METO	NE-FINE-COMP	NE-NESTED	NEL-LIT	NEL-METO	MISC
# hipe2022:original_source = data/preparation/corpus/en/retokenized/sophoclesplaysa05campgoog_0098.xmi
# hipe2022:license = CC-BY
# hipe2022:language = en
# hipe2022:document_type = commentary
# hipe2022:document_id = sophoclesplaysa05campgoog_0098
# hipe2022:date = 1896-01-01
# hipe2022:dataset = ajmc
# hipe2022:applicable_columns = TOKEN NE-COARSE-LIT NE-FINE-LIT NE-NESTED NEL-LIT MISC
# ajmc:version = v0.2
# ajmc:title = Sophocles: The Plays and Fragments
# ajmc:publication_place = London
# ajmc:publication_date = 1896
# ajmc:page = 98
# ajmc:author = Jebb, Richard Claverhouse
16	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ξυναρπάζω	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
φρενί	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
expresses	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
thrill	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
instant	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
recognition	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
voice	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
falls	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
distinctly	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
εὐμαθὲς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
on	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
his	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ear	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
also	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
suggests	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
emotion	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
joy	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
For	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
verb	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Simylus	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q11950657	_	LED0.00
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
poet	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Middle	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Comedy	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ap	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Stobaeus	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q444079	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Flor	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q107029507	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q107029507	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
360	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Σ6	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ρ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ζξέψώο	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ὲξς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πάσαι	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
17	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κώδωνος	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Τωρσηνικῆς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
trumE:2a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
R3Pr	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
kk	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
diameter	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ending	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
bel	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
shaped	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
aperture	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
κώδων	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
“	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
Tyrrhenian	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
frequent	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
epithet	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
trumpet	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
Aesch	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q40939	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q40939	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Eum	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q1233164	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q1233164	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
567	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Eur	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q48305	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q48305	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Phoen	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1233660	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1233660	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
1377	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Very	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q1398	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.20
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q1398	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.20
Aen	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q60220	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q60220	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
8	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
526	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
etc	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
perhaps	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
means	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
no	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
more	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
than	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
that	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
instrument	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
was	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
first	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
brought	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Europe	B-loc	_	B-loc	_	_	O	Q46	_	LED0.00
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Tyrrheniam	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
pirates	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ληστοσαλπιγκταίof	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Menander	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q118992	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter
frag	B-work	_	B-work.fragm	_	_	O	NIL	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.fragm	_	_	O	NIL	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
incert	I-work	_	I-work.fragm	_	_	O	NIL	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.fragm	_	_	O	NIL	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
399	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Tyrheni	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
according	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
tra	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
dition	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
for	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
which	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Herodotus	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q26825	_	LED0.00
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
earliest	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
witnes	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
I	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
94	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
were	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Lydiam	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
origin	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
bronze	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
trumpet	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
may	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
have	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
been	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Lydiam	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
invention	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
see	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Dict	B-work	_	B-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|LED0.00
Ant	I-work	_	I-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|LED0.00
“	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter
Tuba	B-work	_	B-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
Homer	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q6691	_	LED0.00
mentions	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
trumpet	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
only	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
similes	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
when	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
voice	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Achilles	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q41746	_	LED0.00
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
likened	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
Il	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q8275	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q8275	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
18	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.08
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.08
219	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.08
,	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.08
etc	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.08
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.08
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
But	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Greeks	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
must	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
have	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
had	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
early	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
at	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
least	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
time	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Dorian	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
conquest	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
judge	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
from	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
legends	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
heard	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Pausanias	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q192931	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
at	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Agos	B-loc	_	B-loc	_	_	O	Q13533353	_	LED0.20
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
2	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.20
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.20
21	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.20
,	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.20
8	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.20
3	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.20
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
vhere	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
there	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
was	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
shrine	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ἀθηνᾷ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Σάλπιγξ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
See	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Appendix	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
As	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
gender	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κώδων	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Arist	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q868	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q868	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
De	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q3481081	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Sens	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q3481081	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q3481081	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
6	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.08
p	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.08
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.08
4466	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.08
22	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.08
has	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
τῆς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κώδωνος	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
bel	B-pers	_	B-pers.editor	_	_	O	NIL	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.25
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
In	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ar	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q43353	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q43353	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Bax	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1193602	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.33
1078	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
words	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
χὴ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κώδων	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀκαλανθίς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
are	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
said	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
mean	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
kind	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
hound	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
But	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κώδων	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
bel	B-pers	_	B-pers.editor	_	_	O	NIL	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.25
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
masc	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
with	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Thuc	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q41683	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q41683	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q41683	_	LED0.00
Strabo	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q45936	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Plutarch	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q41523	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Diodorus	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q171241	_	LED0.00
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
ξ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
εσηα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
υυιε	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
αυαοωςο	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οἱ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
act	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
observed	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ten	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q129772	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.25
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q129772	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.25
Cyr	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1145374	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1145374	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
8	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
I	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
33	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
ἐπέγνως	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
δ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἂν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
οὐδένα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οὔτε	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ὀργιζόμενον	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
2	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
2S	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Eea2	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
4	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
1296	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence|LED0.00
Remark	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
εὖ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
syl	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
4th	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
foot	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
referring	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
word	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
before	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
95	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ant	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q241077	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q241077	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
166	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
723	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
19	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
βόσιν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κυκλοῶντ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
moving	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
round	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
round	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
going	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
backwards	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
forwards	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
attempt	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
make	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
out	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
footprints	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
like	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
hound	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
questing	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
about	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
for	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
scent	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ant	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q241077	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q241077	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
226	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
ὁδοῖς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κυκλῶν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἐμαυτὸν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
εἰς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀναστροφήν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
Eur	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q48305	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q48305	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Or	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q663886	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q663886	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
632	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
ποῖ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
σὸν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πόδ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἐπὶ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
συννοίᾳ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κυκλεῖς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
‘pacing	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
fro	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
meditation	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
‖	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
διπλῆς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
μερίμνης	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
διπτύχους	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἰὼν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ὁδούς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
τῷ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
σακεσφόρῳ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Il	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q8275	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q8275	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
7	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
219	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Αἴας	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
δ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
δ’ἐγγύθεν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
ἦλθε	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
φέρων	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
σἀκος	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἠύτε	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πύργον	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
‖χάλκέον,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
ἐπταβόειον	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
ε	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
made	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
stitching	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
together	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
seven	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
layers	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ox	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
hide	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
then	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
covering	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
outer	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
face	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
with	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
plates	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
bronze	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
Cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
576	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ovid	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q7198	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Met	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q184742	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q184742	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
13	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
2	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
clypei	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
dominus	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
septemplicis	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Afiax	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
a1	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
f	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀσκόπου	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
inconceivable	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
unimaginable	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
horror	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
El	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q733444	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q733444	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
864	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
ἄσκοπος	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
λώβα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἔκει	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
περάνας	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
sa	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
perfect	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
O	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
T	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
577	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
n	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
double	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
acc	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
with	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
