TOKEN	NE-COARSE-LIT	NE-COARSE-METO	NE-FINE-LIT	NE-FINE-METO	NE-FINE-COMP	NE-NESTED	NEL-LIT	NEL-METO	MISC
# hipe2022:original_source = data/preparation_new/corpus/en/retokenized/sophoclesplaysa05campgoog_0147.xmi
# hipe2022:license = CC-BY
# hipe2022:language = en
# hipe2022:document_type = commentary
# hipe2022:document_id = sophoclesplaysa05campgoog_0147
# hipe2022:date = 1896-01-01
# hipe2022:dataset = ajmc
# hipe2022:applicable_columns = TOKEN NE-COARSE-LIT NE-FINE-LIT NE-NESTED NEL-LIT MISC
# ajmc:version = v0.3
# ajmc:title = Sophocles: The Plays and Fragments
# ajmc:publication_place = London
# ajmc:publication_date = 1896
# ajmc:page = 147
# ajmc:author = Jebb, Richard Claverhouse
ἑαυτὸν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
διαφθεῖραι	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
picture	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
vas	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
at	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Cyzicus	B-loc	_	B-loc	_	_	O	Q615449	_	LED0.00
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
70	B-date	_	B-date	_	_	O	_	_	LED0.00
B	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
C	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	LED0.00
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
Cic	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q1541	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q1541	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
In	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1581567	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Verr	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1581567	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1581567	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
2	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
4	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
60	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
but	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
vas	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
afterwards	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
bought	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Juliue	B-pers	_	B-pers.other	_	_	O	Q1048	_	LED0.08
Caesar	I-pers	_	I-pers.other	_	_	O	Q1048	_	LED0.08
for	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Temple	B-loc	_	B-loc	_	_	O	Q2459870	_	LED0.00
of	I-loc	_	I-loc	_	_	O	Q2459870	_	LED0.00
Venus	I-loc	_	I-loc	_	_	B-pers.myth	Q2459870	_	LED0.00
Genetrix	I-loc	_	I-loc	_	_	I-pers.myth	Q2459870	_	LED0.00
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Rome	B-loc	_	B-loc	_	_	O	Q220	_	LED0.00
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
Plin	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q82778	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q82778	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
W	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q442	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.20
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q442	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.20
H	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q442	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.20
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q442	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.20
7	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
38	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
§	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
126	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
See	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Introduction	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|LED0.00
§	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|LED0.00
20	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
222	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
429	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
This	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
kommos	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
serves	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
like	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
last	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
201	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
-	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
262	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
lyric	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
expression	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
tragic	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
pathos	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
after	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
which	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
situation	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
further	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
developed	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
former	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
case	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
iambic	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
dialogue	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
But	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
one	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
respect	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
this	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
kommos	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
differs	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
from	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
its	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
predecessor.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
In	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
order	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
bring	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
mind	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ajax	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q172725	_	LED0.00
into	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
fiuler	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
relief	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
lyrics	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
are	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
given	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
him	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
alone	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
while	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Chorus	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Tecmesa	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q10796858	_	LED0.00
speak	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
only	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
trimeters	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
structure	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
follows	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
1ststrophe	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
348	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
-	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
355	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
=	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
1st	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
antisr	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
356	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
-	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
363	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
sr	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
364	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
-	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
378	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
=	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ant	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
379	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
-	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
393	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
3rd	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
atr	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
394	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
-	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
411	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
=	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
3rd	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ant	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
412	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
-	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
429	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
For	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
metres	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
see	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Metrical	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Analysis	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
888	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ff	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἰὼ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
φίλοι	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ναυβάται	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
his	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
first	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
words	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
mark	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
affection	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
which	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
was	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
so	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
deep	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
rugged	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
nature	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἐμμένουτες·	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
O	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
T	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
351	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
τῷ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κηρύγματι	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἐμμένειν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
ὁρβῷ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
νόμῳ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
right	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
sound	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
rule	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ofloyalty	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
friendship	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
which	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Greek	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
chiefs	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
have	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
forsaken	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
261	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ff	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἴδεσθέ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
μ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
for	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
this	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
nidd	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
aot	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ph	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1415903	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1415903	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
351	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
n	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
constr	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Aesch	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q40939	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q40939	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
P	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q846870	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.20
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q846870	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.20
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q846870	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.20
92	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
θέσθε	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
μ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἴα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πρὸς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
θεῶν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πάσχω	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
θεός	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
—	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
κῶμα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
bloodshed	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἄλης	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
storm	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
frenzy	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
which	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
was	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
caused	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Pind	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q134929	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q134929	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
O	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q18146776	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q18146776	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
12	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.29
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.29
1r	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.29
οἴ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
δ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀνιαραῖς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
‖	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀντικύρσαντες	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἄλαις	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἐσλὸν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
βαθὺ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πήματος	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἐν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
μικρῷ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
πεδάμειψαν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
χρόνῳ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
epithet	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
φοιίας	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
denoting	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
fxi	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
he	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἄλη	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
i	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
e	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
vealy	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
belonging	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
sense	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κῦμα	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
has	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
more	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
vivid	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
fitness	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
than	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
O	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
T	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q148643	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
24	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
where	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
βυθῶν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
φοινίου	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
σάλου	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
meant	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
pestilence	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
ἀμφίδρομον	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
‘running	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
around	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
me	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence|NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κυκλεῖται	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
this	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
rare	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
nidd	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
read	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Her	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q26825	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q26825	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
8	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
16	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
μηνοειδὲς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ποιήσαντες	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
τῶν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
νεὼν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἐκυκλεῦντο	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ὡς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
περιλάβοιεν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
αὐτούς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
But	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
fr	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
787	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
2	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
κυκλεῖται	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
pass	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
so	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ellendt	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q18411800	_	LED0.00
would	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
take	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
here	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
‘is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
rolled	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
around	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
me	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence|NoSpaceAfter
—	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
needlessly	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
I	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
think	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κυκλοὗτοι	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
would	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
be	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
more	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
usual	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
stdd	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
form	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
Her	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q26825	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q26825	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
3	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
157	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
oft	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
664	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ft	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οἴμ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
this	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
elision	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
occurs	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
587	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ant	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q241077	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q241077	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
320	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
1270	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ar	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q43353	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q43353	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Aci	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1059987	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.25
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1059987	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.25
590	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
Though	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
breaks	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
rule	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Tragedy	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
against	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
eliding	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
diphthonss	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
was	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
doubtless	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
too	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
familiar	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
offend	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ear	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οἳ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἐμὲ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
δειλήν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Anth	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
9	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
408	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
does	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
not	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
warant	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
us	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
supposing	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
that	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οἴμ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
=	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
ο	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
με	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
ἀφρουτίστως	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
fkει	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Tr	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q945342	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q945342	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
366	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
πέμπων	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
οὐκ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀφροντίστως	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
:	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ten	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q129772	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.25
.	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q129772	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.25
Cyr	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1145374	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1145374	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
I	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
6	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
42	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
μηδέποτ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
οὖν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀφρουτίστως	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἔχε	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
‘never	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
be	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
heedless	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence|NoSpaceAfter
For	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
pass	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
form	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
word	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
cp	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
δυσλόγιστον	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
40	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
n	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
It	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
not	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
easy	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
decide	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
whether	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
subject	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἔχει	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ajax	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q172725	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
or	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
τοργον	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
but	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
usage	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
adverb	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
rather	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
favours	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
view	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
that	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ajax	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q172725	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
phrase	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
designedly	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
euphemistic	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
reticent	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
eφ7	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
νᾶς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ἀρωὴὲν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
τέχνας	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
helpfiul	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
