TOKEN	NE-COARSE-LIT	NE-COARSE-METO	NE-FINE-LIT	NE-FINE-METO	NE-FINE-COMP	NE-NESTED	NEL-LIT	NEL-METO	MISC
# hipe2022:original_source = data/preparation/corpus/en/retokenized/sophoclesplaysa05campgoog_0088.xmi
# hipe2022:license = CC-BY
# hipe2022:language = en
# hipe2022:document_type = commentary
# hipe2022:document_id = sophoclesplaysa05campgoog_0088
# hipe2022:date = 1896-01-01
# hipe2022:dataset = ajmc
# hipe2022:applicable_columns = TOKEN NE-COARSE-LIT NE-FINE-LIT NE-NESTED NEL-LIT MISC
# ajmc:version = v0.4
# ajmc:title = Sophocles: The Plays and Fragments
# ajmc:publication_place = London
# ajmc:publication_date = 1896
# ajmc:page = 88
# ajmc:author = Jebb, Richard Claverhouse
mentioned	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
elsewhere	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
;	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
but	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Heyne	B-pers	_	B-pers.editor	_	_	O	Q63182	_	LED0.00
identifies	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
it	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
with	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
often	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
quoted	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Αἰθίοπες	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
as	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Memnon	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q506781	_	LED0.00
was	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
king	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
that	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
people	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
this	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
seems	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
very	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
probable	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Aethiopis	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q410483	_	LED0.00
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Arctnus	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q554683	_	LED0.12
would	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
have	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
furnished	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
material	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
3	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
4	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
τῆς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
κρίσεως	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
μὴ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
τυχὼν.διέφθαρται	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
τὴν	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
γνώμην	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
]	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
In	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
play	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
madness	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ajax	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q172725	_	LED0.00
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
not	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
result	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
his	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
disappointment	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
about	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
arms	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
but	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Athena	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q37122	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
s	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
intervention	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
8	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ΜΑΣΙΓO	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ΦΟΡΟΣ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
]	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
At	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
v	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
91	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|LED0.00
Ajax	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q172725	_	LED0.00
enters	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
carrying	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
lash	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
110	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
which	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
he	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
has	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
used	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
on	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
his	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
captives	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
24	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InPrimaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.33
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
ΛΟΕΡΟΥ	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
]	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
‘leser	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Ajax	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q242319	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
son	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Oileus	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q975447	_	LED0.00
king	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Locrians	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
subject	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Αἴας	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	LED0.00
Λοκρός	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	LED0.00
was	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
probably	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
taken	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
from	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
liupersis	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	Q1627579	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
hero	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
attempts	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
drag	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Cassandra	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q170779	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
who	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
carries	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ξόανον	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Athena	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q37122	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
from	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
temple	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
that	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
goddess	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
The	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Greeks	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
threaten	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
stone	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
him	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
when	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
he	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
flies	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
to	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Athena	B-pers	_	B-pers.myth	_	_	O	Q37122	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
s	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
altar	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
He	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
tried	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Greek	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
tribunal	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
acquired	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
see	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Welcker	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference
Gr	B-work	_	B-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|LED0.00
Trag	I-work	_	I-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|LED0.00
I	B-scope	_	B-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.10
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|LED0.10
161	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|LED0.10
f	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.10
.	I-scope	_	I-scope	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.10
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
Δικαίαρχος	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q352621	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
]	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q352621	_	LED0.00
Of	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q352621	_	LED0.00
Messana	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	B-loc	Q352621	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
pupil	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Aristotle	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q868	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
He	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
wrote	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
περὶ	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	LED0.00
Διονυσιακῶν	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	LED0.00
ἀγώνων	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
perhaps	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
same	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
work	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ὑποθέσεις	B-work	_	B-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	LED0.00
τῶν	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	LED0.00
Εὐριπίδου	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	LED0.00
καὶ	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	LED0.00
Σοφοκλέους	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	LED0.00
μύθων	I-work	_	I-work.primlit	_	_	O	NIL	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
9	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
ταῖς	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Διδασκαλίαις	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
]	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
‘Dramatic	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
performances	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
-	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
list	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
of	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
tragedies	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
comedies	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
produced	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
at	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Athens	B-loc	_	B-loc	_	_	O	Q1524	_	LED0.00
in	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
each	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
year	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
Aristotle	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q868	_	LED0.00
compiled	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
a	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
work	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
with	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
this	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
title	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
which	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
is	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
probably	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
meant	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
here	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
Similar	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
lists	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
were	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
drawn	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
up	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
the	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
poet	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Callimachus	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q192417	_	LED0.00
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
260	B-date	_	B-date	_	_	O	_	_	LED0.00
B	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
C	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
by	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Aristophanes	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	Q313018	_	LED0.00
of	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	O	Q313018	_	LED0.00
Byzantium	I-pers	_	I-pers.author	_	_	B-loc	Q313018	_	LED0.00
(	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
c	B-date	_	B-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	LED0.00
200	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	LED0.00
B	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
C	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-date	_	I-date	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
)	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
and	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
others	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
See	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	_
Smith	B-pers	_	B-pers.author	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
’	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter
s	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference
Dict	B-work	_	B-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|LED0.00
Ant	I-work	_	I-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
.	I-work	_	I-work.seclit	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter|LED0.00
,	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference
vol	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference
II	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference
p	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference
865	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	InSecondaryReference|NoSpaceAfter
.	O	_	O	_	_	O	_	_	EndOfSentence
